<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<feature id="com.wireframesketcher" image="sketch_120.png" label="%featureName" plugin="com.wireframesketcher.ui" provider-name="%providerName" version="4.2.5">

   <description>
      %description
   </description>

   <copyright>
      %copyright
   </copyright>

   <license url="license.html"><![CDATA[WireframeSketcher License Agreement

This License Agreement is a legal contract between you (either as an individual
or a single entity) and PETRU SEVERIN ("PETRU SEVERIN") for the
WireframeSketcher software ("Software") and related on-line or printed
documentation.

You should carefully read the following terms and conditions before using the
Software. If you do not agree to these terms, then delete and destroy all copies
of the Software and related documentation in your possession. Upon your
certification to PETRU SEVERIN that you have not used the Software you do not
accept this license agreement and have deleted and destroyed all copies of the
software and related documentation, your money will be refunded.

The Software is protected by copyright laws and international copyright
treaties, as well as other intellectual property laws and treaties. The Software
is licensed, not sold.

Evaluation License

This is NOT a free software. Subject to the terms below, you are hereby licensed
to use the Software for evaluation purposes without charge. To use the Software
for commercial purposes a registration is required.

License Grant

Single-User License

If you are an individual and this Agreement is for a Single-User license, you
may install the Software on multiple computers that those computers are solely
for your own use.

Multi-User (Volume) License

If this Agreement is for a Multi-User (Volume) license, the number of named
users which use the Software may not exceed the number of licenses purchased,
regardless of the number of computers the Software is installed on. Licenses are
named and transferable.

Site License

If this Agreement is for a Site license, the number of users which use the
Software and the number of Software installations within the licensed entity is
unlimited.

Maintenance

Any License is subject to 12 months of maintenance period which includes e-mail
support, software updates and access to online services. As maintenance period
expires it can be optionally renewed at a discounted price. Maintenance renewals
commence from the expiration date of the previous maintenance period.

Distribution

Provided that you are distributing the evaluation version and NOT the registered
version, you are hereby licensed to make as many copies of the evaluation
version of the Software as you wish; give exact copies of the original
evaluation version to anyone; and distribute the evaluation version of the
Software in its unmodified form via electronic means. There is no charge for any
of the above.

You are specifically prohibited from charging, or requesting donations, for any
such copies, however made; and from distributing the Software with other
products (commercial or otherwise) without prior written permission.

You may NOT redistribute any derivative works of the Software without prior
written permission from PETRU SEVERIN.

DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY

PETRU SEVERIN EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTY FOR THE SOFTWARE. THE SOFTWARE
AND ANY RELATED DOCUMENTATION IS PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. THE
ENTIRE RISK ARISING OUT OF USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE SOFTWARE REMAINS WITH YOU.

LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL PETRU
SEVERIN OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR
LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION,
ANY OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS, ATTORNEY FEES AND COURT COSTS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE
OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SOFTWARE OR THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE
SUPPORT SERVICES, EVEN IF PETRU SEVERIN HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF
SUCH DAMAGES.

General

This License Agreement will be governed by the laws of Romania. This License
Agreement may only be modified by a license addendum, which accompanies this
License Agreement or by a written document which has been signed, by both you
and PETRU SEVERIN. This License Agreement has been written in the English
language only and is not to be translated or interpreted in any other language.
Prices, costs and fees for use of WireframeSketcher are subject to change
without notice to you. In the event of invalidity of any provision of this
License Agreement, the invalidity shall not affect the validity of the remaining
portions of this License Agreement.

]]></license>

   <url>
      <update label="%updateSiteName" url="http://wireframesketcher.com/updates"/>
      <discovery label="%updateSiteName" url="http://wireframesketcher.com/updates"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.filesystem"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.gef"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.views"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.forms"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.help"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ltk.core.refactoring"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.draw2d"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore.xmi"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.commons.httpclient"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin download-size="6651" id="com.wireframesketcher.ui" install-size="6651" unpack="false" version="4.2.5"/>

   <plugin download-size="504" id="com.wireframesketcher.model" install-size="504" unpack="false" version="4.2.5"/>

   <plugin download-size="20" id="com.wireframesketcher.spy" install-size="20" unpack="false" version="4.2.5"/>

</feature>
